

CONTACT

+63 998 510 3055



mdgudez@gmail.com

EXPERTISE

Scheduling and Time

Data Analytics

Web Development

Effective Communication

PERSONAL SKILLS

Team building

EDUCATION

Undergraduate of Bachelor of Science in Mechanical

MARK DANIEL GUDEZ

Technical Project Manager

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/mark-gudez/

https://markymarkph.github.io

https://www.upwork.com/freelancers/~016604e6338affff6f

PERSONAL PROFILE

Strategic and detail-oriented Project Manager with 7+ years of experience in Web Development. Outstanding organizational, time management, planning, and problem-solving skills. Met all project deadlines for all projects assigned to me. Experienced manager handling a team of Data Analysts and Web Developers.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT SUPERVISOR

Premium Megastructures Inc | Feb 2019 - Aug 2020

- Developing and overseeing the installation of systems, which include software and hardware
- Implementing safety procedures and data recovery plans.
- Analyzing existing computer systems and making recommendations for upgrades and improvements.
- Collaborating with other departments and professionals in the development of IT systems.
- Ensuring all installations, maintenance, and upgrades are carried out on schedule and to client specifications.

TECHNICAL LEAD DEVELOPER

Creative Synergy General Merchandise | June 2015 - Dec 2016

- Determining project requirements and developing work schedules
- Delegating tasks and achieving daily, weekly, and monthly goals.
- Analyzing existing operations and scheduling training sessions and meetings to discuss improvements.
- Keeping up-to-date with industry trends and developments.
- Being transparent with the team about challenges, failures, and successes
- Build healthy & lasting relationships with the team.
- Helping with day-to-day project tasks.

DATA ANALYST - TEAM LEAD

Outsourced Quality Assured Services | Feb 2014 - May 2015

- Develop and implement databases, data collection systems, data analytics and other strategies that optimize statistical efficiency and quality
- Acquiring data from primary or secondary data sources and maintaining databases
- Identify, analyze, and interpret trends or patterns in complex data
- Interpretation of data, analyze results using statistical techniques and provide ongoing reports
- Helping with day-to-day project tasks

Signature-